Bart Got a Room is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Brian Hecker.
High school loser Danny Stein needs a prom date.
As a cause of anxiety for Danny, Bart Beeber, the nerdiest
guy in school, has already found a date.
At the same time, Danny's divorced parents are both seeking relationships again.
Danny, played by Steven Kaplan.
Ernie Stein, played by William H. Macy.
Beth Stein, played by Cheryl Hines.
Alice, played by Ashley Benson.
Camille, played by Alia Shawkat.
Craig, played by Brandon Hardesty.
Bart Got a Room is a 2008 comedy film written and directed by Brian
Hecker, and stars Steven Kaplan, Alia Shawkat, William H.
Macy, and Cheryl Hines.
Also appearing in the film are Ashley Benson, Brandon Hardesty, Kate Micucci, Jennifer Tilly,
Dinah Manoff (in her last film role as of 2022) and Chad Jamian Williams as Bart.
The film premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival on April 25, 2008.
It had a limited US release in select theaters on April 3,
2009, and was released on DVD on July 28, 2009.
The film explores themes of high school, date,
coming of age, prom, divorced parents.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.